JOE: Hey, yo, man, wake up.
Hey, man, you gotta get up,
aight?
You gotta leave.
It's getting late.
(bottles and cans clattering)
Wh--
What time is it?
It's like noon.
Look, the party was straight
and everything,
but now I got to clean up
all this shit.
(chuckles)
I mean, it's like
I know y'all,
but I don't know y'all,
you know?
I mean, we cool,
but we ain't cool.
(bottles clang)
Where is Alfred?
Who?
Al.
Paper Boi.
Oh, he dipped
a while ago.
You know, it's like
y'all my niggas,
but y'all ain't my niggas.
I mean it's like
I know y'all,
but I don't know y'all,
man.
(bottles clang)
Where's my jacket?
JOE:
People just tearing up shit.
Somebody poured a beer
in my Brita pitcher.
I mean it's like
I fuck with y'all,
but I don't fuck with y'all,
man!
It's a...
It's like a--
a blue bomber jacket.
-Have you seen it?
-Nah.
But I did see when somebody
tried to light my trash can
on fire.
(bottles clang)
-What?
-Yeah.
It's all burned up
on the inside.
(chuckles)
I mean, I was gonna
get another one anyway,
but--
but that's besides
the point.
I mean, it's like
we boys, but--
But we ain't boys.
Yeah, I get it.
Have you seen--
it's got a patch on it.
You know?
Like a seal--
Can we hurry up
and get some food?
I'm, like, dying.
(women indistinctly arguing
outside)
("Broccoli"
by D.R.A.M. playing)
* Hey, lil' Mama
* Would you like to be
my sunshine? *
* Nigga touch my gang
we gon' turn this shit *
* To Columbine *
* Hey, hey
(line trilling)
Hey.
What's up, Al?
Um, did you pick up my jacket
yesterday?
(indistinct speech over phone)
Dang.
No, I just--I just thought
maybe you picked it up.
Um...
I'm just gonna--
I'm gonna retrace my steps,
try and see if I can find it.
All right?
All right, cool.
Peace.
Free chicken sandwich day,
nigga.
(music playing inside)
-Hey, what's--
-Listen, you owe me $10, man.
No, I mean--
I was here last night.
I think I left my jacket
in there.
Still got to
charge you ten.
Come on, man,
Can't you just look?
(hip-hop music playing)
Nope.
Didn't see it.
W--
I really need this jacket.
(music continues)
Nah, man.
It ain't here.
Enjoy.
* Flippin' all night, boy,
I'll be flippin' all night *
* After I flip all night, boy,
* Flippin' all night, boy,
I'll be flippin' all night *
Hey, honey.
You want a dance?
Uh, no, actually,
I was here last night.
I'm--I'm just lookin'
for my jacket.
Oh, with Paper Boi?
I heard he was in here.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm--I'm his manager.
(scoffs)
Oh, really?
Y'all need a girl
for a music video?
'Cause I'll do it.
Uh, nah.
Maybe.
I'll keep you in mind.
Okay, don't lie to me.
I'm--I'm not lying to you.
Look,
are any of the girls
from last night here right now?
One of them might have
my jacket.
Okay, what she look like?
She--
she was blonde.
She had blonde hair.
Was it short blonde hair?
Uh...
No, it was--
it stopped at, like,
her...shoulders.
Nah.
Well, wait.
She like a hot yellow broad?
She was
kind of light-skinned,
but not--
not super light-skinned.
Okay, was she thick?
Was she skinny?
She was pretty thick.
Big titties?
Not the biggest titties.
Like, they were--
they were--
they were pretty big, yeah.
Was she tall
with a fat ass?
Kind of.
I don't know.
She--
She was like her.
She l--
she looked like her.
Nigga, them titties ain't big.
I--whatever.
I don't--
I don't know
the titty median here.
I've been working here
for two years,
and I ain't never seen nobody
that look like that.
Sorry.
Aight.
It's cool.
Thanks.
Uh, wait a minute.
You just gonna leave
and not take my phone number
for the music video?
Oh.
Uh, yeah.
See, you think
I'm playin'.
-I'm so serious.
-I know.
-You better call me.
-Okay.
Told ya.
(music playing inside)
(cell phone unlocks, clicks)
Shots gon' make this night!
Tittys and bittys
and tittys.
Tittys
and bittys and tittys.
Tittys and bittys
and--no, not--
(indistinct chatter)
I hate shots.
You know that, right?
(hip-hop music playing)
*
-Hey.
-What you doing?
(indistinct chatter, cheering)
Gotta get in the Uber!
-Whoo!
-(laughs)
-I got shotgun.
-I got shotgun, nigga.
-I got the front.
-Man.
That's right, man,
to the back.
Hey, man.
Hey, what's your name, man?
What you doin'?
My baby mama's cousin
gonna drop me off.
This nigga, man.
Hey!
(Nelly's "Ride Wit Me" playing)
This is Beyoncé's best song.
Nigga...
(laughs)
But I stay gold!
-* In the back of the Doz-E
-Hey!
* Oh, why
do I feel this good? *
all:
* Hey, must be the money!
(all barking)
Yeah, yeah!
* Yeah, yeah
(all barking)
What if we found out
Ja Rule was just a dog?
(laughter)
-Like, he's just--
-Like--
(indistinct noises from video)
-Nigga, grunk!
-Look at this shit.
-I wanna see--
-Oh! Watch what they doin'--
(hip-hop music playing)
Hey, come on!
I said it. Look at that.
Look at that. Look at that.
No. No, you don't understand.
It takes your soul, man.
(hip-hop music from phone)
(humming)
Yo!
E-money.
-Hey.
-What it be like?
-Hey, guys.
-Sup, bro?
Sup?
Thanks for waking me up
this morning.
We didn't wake you up.
Yeah, I know.
(sighs)
I woke up at 11:30
with Joe screaming at me.
-Word?
-Yeah, he was pretty mad.
Why?
'Cause we, like,
ruined his house.
Like, we set, like, a trash can
on fire or something?
-Right.
-(laughs)
Oh, yeah, that did happen.
-Yeah.
-Yep.
Hey, that girl, Kim,
threw that blunt in the trash.
-Mm.
-(laughs)
-Man, we was drunk as hell.
-That was cold.
Yeah, well, he's pissed.
Well, so what?
Fuck him, man.
I can barely remember
last night, man.
Well, you don't need to.
You Snapchatted the whole thing.
Uh, yup.
How else we gonna
let niggas know
how we livin' out here?
(chuckles)
Most of this rap shit
is appearances, right?
Yeah, appearances of money.
Look, we need to start
stuntin' on niggas more.
All right?
That's what we need to do, bro.
Stunting's a kind of a trap.
We should probably
make a little bit more money
before we start showing it off.
Oh, my God, man.
How you suck the fun
out of everything.
See, that's--
that's black people's
number one problem.
Man, they don't know
how to have fun.
I really disagree
with that being black people's
number one problem.
-See how he goes?
-You know what I think?
I think if we spent
the time we spend
thinking about not spending
money, spent that time
on spending money,
then it'd be time well spent.
But all the rest of that--
you know, I--
Here, let me see your phone.
I need to contact that
Uber driver from last night.
I think he's got my jacket.
Thanks.
Don't flip through
my photos, man.
Let me get some of them, man.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Speaking of money,
how you think these sunflower
seed companies make money?
-They're only 75¢ a pack.
-Hey.
Um, yeah, this is, uh,
a customer of yours
from last night.
Uh, yeah, I think--
yeah, the rappers.
The rappers.
I think I left a--
a jacket in there?
It's a--
it's like navy blue bomber.
And now they're coming out
with all of these
different flavors.
-You got barbecue.
-Yeah, check, please.
-Thanks.
-Teriyaki.
-Mmm.
-Sushi.
-Sushi, nigga?
-Catfish.
You got all kinds
of different brands.
I don't know if I want
no sushi seeds, man.
No, they're delicious.
-Sushi sunflower seeds?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Hey, why you didn't get those?
-Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, I'm--
Yeah, I was looking
all over for it.
Uh, could you bring it to,
uh, 24--
Don't really
support sushi.
-I think it's a bigger issue...
-Uh, all right.
-Than people talk about.
-But how is it--wait, man.
-Yeah, okay.
-It's not like they killing
the sushi and putting them
in the seed, bro.
-Oh, so that's artificial?
-That's artificial.
-All right.
-Hmm.
Yeah. Bye.
Damn it.
I wonder why the--
there's--
it's not real sushi.
It's all right, man.
It's okay.
Found my jacket.
both: Hey!
Brap!
He wants me to pay $50
to drop it off.
Damn.
-Wait, Fidel from last night?
-Yeah.
-F-money?
-Ooh, these Uber niggas
is ruthless, boy.
-I was hoping maybe you'd...
-(blows raspberries)
Drive me down there.
-Oh, Earn, man, God.
-Please.
I hate that sound--
like, that sound, like, come on.
Alfred, I really need
this jacket, man.
(groans)
Aight, man,
I guess, man.
Here we go.
-Bailin' his ass out again.
-I guess.
Man, you didn't even
bail my ass out
when I was actually in jail.
What do you mean, "I guess"?
I guess we're
doing this again.
Oh, hey, man, we can go
get some Jamaican food, boy.
(Jamaican accent)
Oh, Jamaican.
-Hell yeah.
-The curry goat.
The curry goat.
I wonder how they catch
those goats, man.
Yo, where is this nigga,
man?
This some bull.
Uh, he told me
to meet him here.
I don't know if one of these
is his houses or what.
Well, call his ass again.
This negro stakeout shit
shouldn't take this long
for no jacket.
48 Hrs.
All black cast.
Does that even work?
(chimes ringing on phone)
Oh.
It's probably him.
SENATOR K: Second time it's me.
-Hello?
SENATOR K:
Hey, is this Earnest Marks?
Uh, yeah.
Who's this?
SENATOR K:
It's me, uh, you know?
Senator K.
(laughs)
Yeah, the rapper.
You manage Paper Boi, right?
I love his music.
Tell him
we'll work on something.
EARNEST: Uh, that'd be dope.
SENATOR K: Yo, man, you guys
should come to Chicago.
Yeah, that--
are you asking us on tour?
SENATOR K: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, just get ready, man.
Aight, just think it.
Yo.
That was Senator K.
He wants to go
on tour with you.
Wait, Senator K?
Yo!
That boy's music is fuego!
What, you see Fidel?
No.
Uh-uh.
Something off.
No, man.
(engine turns over)
What? Wait.
What are you talking about?
(sirens chirp)
(tires screech)
(all exclaim)
MAN: Move! Move! Move!
Get out of the car.
Put your hands up now.
(indistinct yelling)
Atlanta PD!
Hey, man, chill out!
Driver, I need you
to turn off the car.
I need everybody
to get out slowly.
All right,
I'm turning off the car, man.
-I got your six!
-Hands up!
Dude, you don't got to point
the damn guns, man.
Slowly, gentlemen.
Turn around.
-Put your hands on the car.
-Step it out!
Look, my hands right here, man.
Hey, what the hell
is going on?
What are you gentlemen
doing down here?
Man, we're just waiting
on our Uber driver.
Open your legs.
Do you have any weapons
or narcotics on you?
What?
Do you gentlemen know
Fidel Arroyo?
F-money?
Hey, hey, yo, yo!
What you doing to my car, man?
It's a safety precaution.
MAN: Are you guys here
to purchase drugs
or weapons from Mr. Arroyo?
We here for a jacket.
My jacket.
-There he goes.
-Get down!
Take him, take him, take him!
(gunshots)
-Oh!
-Ooh!
-Coming in.
-Checking for weapons!
-Yo, come on.
-Clear the area!
Did y'all really need
all them bullets, man?
(dog barking)
Just stay there, sir.
(indistinct radio chatter)
MAN: Keep an eye on
that bush line!
MAN: Suspect is down.
Repeat, suspect is down.
(screams)
Get up!
-He's dead.
-Don't touch me!
Why?
(sobbing)
-Ma'am, it's okay.
-(baby crying)
(sighs)
Four suspects...
(helicopter hovering)
Could you--
could you check his pockets?
That's my jacket.
Could you check in--
could you check
in his pockets?
His pockets--
like, is--
I left something in it--
in the pockets.
(baby crying)
(woman sobbing)
There's nothing.
-All right, thank you.
-I'm gonna ask you to leave.
-It's like a secret pocket in--
MAN: All right. No.
-Back up.
MAN: No. Go.
Go.
(police radio chatter)
ALFRED: (sighs)
Sorry about the jacket,
man.
That whole thing was,
uh...
(sighs)
Pretty crazy, though.
-And cool.
ALFRED: Yeah.
Yeah, it was a little cool.
(chuckles)
It's fine.
I'm not even mad
about the jacket.
Hey, man.
It's for you.
For what?
It's your 5%,
or whatever.
This is a lot.
It's all yours.
Yeah, yeah, I think
I'm gonna go in the house.
I ate them two blunts
when the cops came.
So tonight--tonight's
gonna be weird.
(laughs)
Are you coming in?
No, I'm--
I'm going to Van's
and Lottie's tonight.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Daddy day care?
-Daddy day care.
-Yeah.
-Warm the bottles up.
(chuckles)
You did good, man.
I'll catch you.
All right.
(dog barking)
WOMAN: Harry, stop it!
Stop it.
(dog barking)
(R&B music playing)
(indistinct chatter)
You gonna try?
Right off the grill.
-Mmm.
-Yeah.
-Mmm!
Look what Daddy cooked us.
-Right? Mmm.
-That actually smells good.
Yummy!
-Yummy!
-Want a little piece, baby?
Yummy?
You haven't even tried it yet.
(sighs)
Where did you learn
to cook like this?
Uh, remember that show
Down Home with the Neelys?
Yeah, that was like--
you want some, baby?
Mmm!
No, I used to--
I used to swing with them,
so, like, I learned some things.
-Oh.
-How is it?
Is it good?
-(laughs)
-It is.
-I think it probably--
-He didn't inhale.
He didn't.
both: No.
It's raining really hard
in this movie.
(rhythmic knocking on door)
-Who's that?
-Swift.
-Hey.
-What's up?
What's up, man?
What's up, boy?
What's good, brother?
Hey.
Here you go,
your key.
Thank you.
I've been looking
all day for this.
Yeah, your drunk ass
told me to keep it
last night in the club.
You done outsmarted
yourself again.
Yeah.
Again.
Yeah, look, so what's up?
You coming to work tomorrow?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I guess.
All right.
Well, bet, man,
I'll see you up there.
-All right, man.
-Hey.
Tell your cousin that
party was crazy last night.
I will. I will.
Hey, what's up,
Vanessa?
(chuckles)
Hi, Justin.
How you doin'?
(chuckles)
Lookin' all--
hey, look,
if y'all ever break up--
would that be weird?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Call me "Swift," baby.
-I will.
-She got a sister?
-Nah.
Mm.
So y'all were wasted last night?
Kinda.
Not really.
(groans)
Oh, by the way...
This is for you.
What is that?
It's that thing
we always need.
(laughs)
You a drug dealer now?
Earn, are you kidding me?
(laughs)
-Are you--
-Oh, my God.
-Yo, you are fucking wack.
-You looked so sad.
You looked so sad.
I'm really flattered...
(laughs)
That you think
I could sell drugs.
No, I'm not--
come on.
You think I really
could do that?
I'd be so bad at it.
(laughs)
I hate you.
I know.
(sighs)
You're a good daddy,
though.
You know you can stay
the night, right?
Yeah.
It's cool, though.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Okay.
All right.
Have a good night.
You too.
Call you tomorrow.
Okay.
Yeah.
("Elevators (Me & You)"
by OutKast playing)
* *
* One for the money,
yes, sir, two for the show *
* A couple of years ago
on Headland and Delowe *
* Was the start
of something good *
* Where me and my (...)
rode the Marta *
* Through the hood
just tryna find that hook up *
* Now every day we looked up
at the ceiling *
* Watching ceiling fans
go round *
* Tryna catch that feeling
off instrumentals *
* Had my pencil
and plus my paper *
* We caught the 86 Lithonia
headed to Decatur *
* Writing rhymes, tryna find
our spot off in that light *
* Light off in that spot,
knowing that we could rock *
* Doing the hole
in the wall clubs *
* This shit here
must stop like, "Freeze!" *
(thunder rumbling)
(door clanging)
("Elevators (Me & You)"
continues)
* *
* Got stopped at the mall
the other day *
* Heard a call from the other
way that I just came from *
* Some (...) was saying
something talking about *
* Smoke something,
"Hey, man, what kinda car *
* "You drive? I know you paid,
I know y'all got *
* Beaucoup of hoes
from all them songs *
* That y'all done made"
And I replied *
* That I had been going through
the same things that he has *
* True, I've got more fans
than the average man *
* But not enough loot to last
me to the end of the week *
* I live by the beat
like you live check to check *
* If you don't move your feet
then I don't eat *
* So we like neck to neck,
yes, we done come a long way *
* Like them slim-ass cigarettes
from Virginia *
* This ain't gon' stop
so we just gon' continue *
* Continue, continue *
* Yo mama and yo cousin too *
* Rolling down the strip
on Vogues *
* Coming up,
slamming Cadillac doors *
* Me and you *
* Yo mama and yo cousin too
* Rolling down the strip
on Vogues *
* Coming up,
slamming Cadillac doors *
* Me and you
* Yo mama and yo cousin too
* Rolling down the strip
on Vogues *
* Coming up,
slamming Cadillac doors *
* Me and you
* Yo mama and yo cousin too
* Rolling down the strip
on Vogues *
* Coming up,
slamming Cadillac doors *
* Me and you
* Yo mama and yo cousin too
* Rolling down the strip
on Vogues *
* Coming up,
slamming Cadillac doors *
(crickets chirping)
(dog barking)